Guide to the Urban and Regional Planning Department records, 1961-1993 RG0101
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Slides, RG0101 Series 3; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  - GW People: Franz Bader, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 177)
  - GW People: Miscellaneous group shot in black and white, undated (Box 1, Folder 178)
  - Maps, models, drawings: 20th and 21st Site Plan, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 179)
  - Maps, models, drawings: Building Age and Text, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 180)
  - Maps, models, drawings: Campus Guide, undated (Box 1, Folder 181)
  - Maps, models, drawings: Design Study-Lighting Fixtures, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 182)
  - Maps, models, drawings: Existing land use, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 183)
  - Maps, models, drawings: Existing zoning planning study, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 184)
  - Maps, models, drawings: Figure Ground, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 185)
  - Maps, models, drawings: Form Determinants, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 186)
  - Maps, models, drawings: GWU and Metro D.C., 1972 (Box 1, Folder 187)
  - Maps, models, drawings: GWU Campus, undated (Box 1, Folder 188)
  - Maps, models, drawings: GWU Campus Models, 1972 -1973 (Box 1, Folder 189)
  - Maps, models, drawings: GWU Concept, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 190)
  - Maps, models, drawings: GWU Entry Plan, undated (Box 1, Folder 191)
  - Maps, models, drawings: GWU Height, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 192)
  - Maps, models, drawings: GWU Master Plan-parking, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 193)
  - Maps, models, drawings: Illustrative Site Plan (Day), 1976 (Box 1, Folder 194)
  - Maps, models, drawings: Illustrative Site Plan (Night), 1972 (Box 1, Folder 195)
  - Maps, models, drawings: Land Ownership, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 196)
  - Maps, models, drawings: Land Use, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 197)
  - Maps, models, drawings: Marcou-illustrated site plans, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 198)
  - Maps, models, drawings: Original plan for block from archives, undated (Box 1, Folder 199)
  - Maps, models, drawings: Open Space Library Quad, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 200)
  - Maps, models, drawings: O.S. System, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 201)
  - Maps, models, drawings: Pennsylvania Ave. Concept, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 202)
  - Maps, models, drawings: Planning Study, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 203)
  - Maps, models, drawings: Planning Study-Land Acquisition, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 204)
  - Maps, models, drawings: Planning Study-Major Peripheral Uses, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 205)
  - Maps, models, drawings: Planning Study-Traffic and Parking, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 206)
  - Maps, models, drawings: Proposed Lighting Plan, undated (Box 1, Folder 207)
  - Maps, models, drawings: Proposed PED. System, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 208)
  - Maps, models, drawings: Proposed Plan for Quad S. Greene, undated (Box 1, Folder 209)
  - Maps, models, drawings: Sketch-17th St. and PA Avenue, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 210)
  - Maps, models, drawings: Sketch-21st St., undated (Box 1, Folder 211)
  - Maps, models, drawings: Sketch-21st and G St, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 212)
  - Maps, models, drawings: Sketch-21st St. Entrance, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 213)
  - Maps, models, drawings: Sketch-1700 block PA Avenue, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 214)
  - Maps, models, drawings: Sketch-1748 PA Avenue, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 215)
  - Maps, models, drawings: Sketch-Lisner Hall, undated (Box 1, Folder 216)
  - Maps, models, drawings: Sketch-Marvin Center, undated (Box 1, Folder 217)
  - Maps, models, drawings: Sketch-Pepco Building, undated (Box 1, Folder 218)
  - Maps, models, drawings: Sketch-University Yard, undated (Box 1, Folder 219)
  - Maps, models, drawings: Sketches-Various buildings, undated (Box 1, Folder 220)
  - Maps, models, drawings: Spatial Image, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 221)
  - Maps, models, drawings: Stage 3-Master Plan, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 222)
  - Maps, models, drawings: Stage 4-Master Plan, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 223)
  - Maps, models, drawings: T.H. Ownership, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 224)
  - Maps, models, drawings: Traffic Volume, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 225)
  - Maps, models, drawings: University Environs, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 226)
  - Maps, models, drawings: University Expansion, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 227)
  - Maps, models, drawings: University Land Use, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 228)
  - Maps, models, drawings: Various slides on maps, 1970 -1972 (Box 1, Folder 229)
  - Maps, models, drawings: Visual Analysis, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 230)
  - Maps, models, drawings: Water System, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 231)
  - Maps, models, drawings: West End: Illustrative Site Plan, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 232)
  - Maps, models, drawings: White House to Watergate-Building Condition, undated (Box 1, Folder 233)
  - Maps, models, drawings: White House to Watergate-Building Heights allowed by zoning, undated (Box 1, Folder 234)
  - Maps, models, drawings: White House to Watergate-Demolitions, 1965 -1977 (Box 1, Folder 235)
  - Maps, models, drawings: White House to Watergate-Existing land use, undated (Box 1, Folder 236)
  - Maps, models, drawings: White House to Watergate-Existing zoning, undated (Box 1, Folder 237)
  - Maps, models, drawings: White House to Watergate-Neighborhood Character, undated (Box 1, Folder 238)
  - Maps, models, drawings: White House to Watergate-Ownership, undated (Box 1, Folder 239)
  - Maps, models, drawings: White House to Watergate-Street Furniture, undated (Box 1, Folder 240)
  - Maps, models, drawings: White House to Watergate-Traffic Volumes, undated (Box 1, Folder 241)
  - Maps, models, drawings: White House to Watergate-Units Per Building, undated (Box 1, Folder 242)
  - Maps, models, drawings: White House to Watergate-Urban Amenities, undated (Box 1, Folder 243)
  - Maps, models, drawings: White House to Watergate-Vacant land and surface packaging, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 244)
  - Maps, models, drawings: White House to Watergate-Zoning Guide Map, undated (Box 1, Folder 245)
  - Maps, models, drawings: Miscellaneous slides, 1975 -1978 (Box 1, Folder 246)
- Departmental files, 1961-1990; RG0101 Series 4; 0.5 Linear feet
  This series includes correspondence, publications, studies, invitations, application, brochures, memorandums, articles, biographical information, proposals, reports, news releases, syllabuses, and a survey. They range in date from 1961 to 1990. They concern the seminars, conferences, teach evaluations, the Department of Urban and Regional Planing, accreditation for the masters of Urban and Regional Planning, a Center for Urban and Regional Studies, course requirements, Del Ray, Historic Preservation programs, and Mt. Pleasant neighborhood, and Dorn C. McGrath, Jr.
  - Government & Business Administration, School of (1966-1990) Urban and Regional Planning Department, 1973 -1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Government & Business Administration, School of (1966-1990) Urban and Regional Planning Department Application for Planning Degree Accreditation, 1987, 10/07/1986 --04/07/1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Government & Business Administration, School of (1966-1990) Urban and Regional Planning Department Brochures, 01/1970 -1982 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Government & Business Administration, School of (1966-1990) Urban and Regional Planning Department History - General, 1964-1967, 1964 --09/23/1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Government & Business Administration, School of (1966-1990) Urban and Regional Planning Department History - General, 1968-1990, 04/10/1968 --05/18/1990 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Government & Business Administration, School of (1966-1990) Urban and Regional Planning Department History - Abstracts of Department Activities, 1968-1980, 1968 -1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Government & Business Administration, School of (1966-1990) Urban and Regional Planning Department Programs, 1961 -09/1979 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Government & Business Administration, School of (1966-1990) Urban and Regional Planning Department Programs Historic Preservation, 1974 -1985 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Government & Business Administration, School of (1966-1990) Urban and Regional Planning Department Publications, 03/1974 -1976 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Government & Business Administration, School of (1966-1990) Urban and Regional Planning Department Publications "Toward a Comprehensive Plan for the Nations' Capital", 1980, 05/1980 (Box 1, Folder 10)